Walt Coburn papers, 1923-1977
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Walt Coburn papers, 1923-1977
AZ 424
Coburn, Walt, 1889-1971
This collection is organized into Works, Correspondence, Printed Materials and Photographs. The bulk of the collection consists of issues of the various pulp western serials in which Coburn's stories appeared and of his manuscript typescripts.
16 linear feet
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
None.
Biographical Note
Walter John Coburn was born in White Sulphur Springs, Montana Territory, on October 23, 1889. His father, a pioneer cattleman, arrived in Montana Territory in 1863 and founded the Circle C Ranch, one of the largest outfits in the Northwest at the time. Walt gained his cowboy experience which served as material for his future fiction and non-fiction stories as a "$40 a month cowhand" on the Circle C.
From his first accepted story in 1922 until the demise of the pulp western serials in the 1950s, Coburn gained a reputation as "king of the pulp westerns." He published more than 1,000 stories and 40 books. At one point he was producing 600,000 published words a year, and he kept that pace up for two decades. His stories were particularly noted for their authenticity to the frontier and range experience.
Coburn first came to Arizona in 1916 and ranched with his brothers in Globe. He moved to Prescott in 1927, spent 35 years in Tucson and returned to Prescott for the last 10 years of his life. Coburn committed suicide at the age of 82 on 25 May 1971. His autobiography, Walt Coburn: Western Word Wrangler, was published posthumously in 1974.
Organization
This collection is organized into three series:
I. Works, 1923-1977
II. Correspondence, 1920-1975
III. Personal Material and Photographs, 1929-1974
Scope and Content Note
This collection is organized into Works, Correspondence, Printed Materials and Photographs. The bulk of the collection consists of issues of the various pulp western serials in which Coburn's stories appeared and of his manuscript typescripts. Most of the magazines contain only tearsheets of his story, and the cover wrappers. The series is not a complete list of his stories, and it is not noted which stories are reprints with different titles. The nine scrapbooks contain articles and stories by Coburn mostly from True West, Frontier Times, and Old West spanning from the late 1960s to the mid-1970s. These items mostly consist of non-fiction accounts of Coburn's cowboy past in Montana and Arizona. The manuscripts consist of original typescripts, drafts and correspondence dealing with Walt Coburn: Word Wrangler of the West, Pioneer Cattleman of Montana, and Stirrup High. Correspondence is chiefly with his friends, other writers, agents and publishers. The photographs include portraits of Coburn, of various friends and acquaintances, and of his home in Tucson.
Access Terms
Coburn, Walt, 1889-1971 -- Archives
Dempsey, Jack, 1895-
Hoxie, Jack, ca. 1885-1965
Santee, Ross, 1889-1965 -- Correspondence
Authors, American -- 20th century
Western stories
Correspondence
Photographs
Scrapbooks
Container List
- Series I: Works, 1923-1977
  - Magazines, 1923-1977
    - Action Stories
      - "Red Wool": 1-24. 1923 (Box 1)
      - "South of the Law Line," 3/12: 15-53. August 1924 (Box 1)
      - "No Man's Law," 57-76. 1924 (Box 1)
      - Letter to the Editor. 1924 (Box 1)
      - "Ride 'Im Cowboy," 4/5:1-43. January 1925 (Box 1)
      - "When My Horns Was Long," 100-106. April 1925 (Box 1)
      - "The Sun-Dance Kid," 1-22. June 1925 (Box 1)
      - "Water," 5/3: 82-91. November 1925 (Box 1)
      - "As the Buzzard Flies," 103-107. May 1926 (Box 1)
      - "Benito's Brown Derby," 70-80. November 1926 (Box 1)
      - "Action Stories," 1-16. September 1927 (Box 1)
      - "He Rides Alone," vii/2: 1-47. October 1927 (Box 1)
      - "The Two O'Clock Kid," 1-13. November 1927 (Box 1)
      - "Riders of Retribution," 64-73. December 1927 (Box 1)
      - "Rannyhan Law," 52-62. January 1928 (Box 1)
      - "The Road Runner," 1-47. February 1928 (Box 1)
      - "The Last White Chip," 37-54. 1928 (Box 1)
      - "The He-Wolf," 3-44. April 1928 (Box 1)
      - "Courage of Cowardice," 62-72. May 1928 (Box 1)
      - "Lights of Despair," 59-70. June 1928 (Box 1)
      - "The Gun Highway," 3-51. August 1928 (Box 1)
      - "Riders of Fortune," 3-43. September 1928 (Box 1)
      - "Soldiers Six," viii/2: 3-39. October 1928 (Box 1)
      - "Border Buzzards," viii/3: 3-47. November 1928 (Box 1)
      - "Outlaws Trails," viii/4: 3-42. December 1928 (Box 1)
      - "Bear Paw," 43-63. January 1929 (Box 1)
      - "Square Guns," 3-42. February 1929 (Box 1)
      - "Montana Mavericks," viii/7: 3-38. March 1929 (Box 1)
      - "Jim Colt--Lawman," 43-64. 1929 (Box 1)
      - "Ghost Ranchero," viii/9: 3-37. May 1929 (Box 1)
      - "Empty guns," 51-71. June 1929 (Box 1)
      - "Law of the Yukon," 45-58. August 1929 (Box 1)
      - "Texas for Texans," 3-39. September 1929 (Box 1)
      - "Trigger Feud," 3-42. October 1929 (Box 1)
      - "Black Jack's Last Bullet," 3-24. November 1929 (Box 1)
      - "The Gun Ghost," xi/4: 5-34. December 1929 (Box 1)
      - "Gun Throwers," 5-41. February 1930 (Box 1)
      - "Warriors of War Bonnet," ix/7: 5-43. 1930 (Box 1)
      - "The Tennessee Kid," 58-74. May 1930 (Box 1)
      - "Senor Satan," ix/10: 3-46. June 1930 (Box 1)
      - "Guns Up," ix/11: 3-37. July 1930 (Box 1)
      - "Sheep!," 3-35. September 1930 (Box 1)
      - "The Badlands Buckaroo," x/2: 3-41. October 1930 (Box 1)
      - "The Shirt Tail Kid," 3-26. November 1930 (Box 1)
      - "Border Wolves," 3-39. 1930 (Box 1)
      - "Gunman's Legion," x/5: 3-32. January 1931 (Box 1)
      - "Ace of Diamonds," 3-41. April 1931 (Box 1)
      - "Masked Men," x/9: 3-38. May 1931 (Box 1)
      - "Pronto," x/10: 3-39. June 1931 (Box 1)
      - "The Texas Hellion," x/11: 3-38. July 1931 (Box 1)
      - "Outlaw," 3-38. August 1931 (Box 1)
      - "The Killer," 3-38. September 1931 (Box 1)
      - "Senor Spy," 3-42. October 1931 (Box 1)
      - "Fire Brand," 3-39. November 1931 (Box 1)
      - "The Long Law," 3-42. 1931 (Box 1)
      - "Unbranded Men," xi/5: 3-42. January 1932 (Box 1)
      - "Wild Brand," 3-36. February 1932 (Box 1)
      - "Booger Face," 3-38. March 1932 (Box 1)
      - "Man Hunt," 3-42. April 1932 (Box 1)
      - " Black Ramrod," 3-40. 1932 (Box 1)
      - "Montana Red," 3-38. 1932 (Box 1)
      - "Guns West," xi/11: 3-39. July 1932 (Box 1)
      - "Gunhawk of the Rio Grande," 4-37. August 1932 (Box 1)
      - "Trigger Tribe," 3-19. September 1932 (Box 1)
      - "Short-Gun Express," 4-20. October 1932 (Box 1)
      - "Rustlers' Syndicate," xii/3: 4-21. November 1932 (Box 1)
      - "Soldiers of Sonora," xii/4: 4-21. December 1932 (Box 1)
      - "The Triple Cross," xii/5: 7-27. November-December 1933 (Box 1)
      - "Phantom Rustlers," 92-105. December 1934 (Box 1)
      - "I Bury the Dead," 92-99. May-June 1934 (Box 1)
      - "The Blizzard Rider," 47-57. April 1934 (Box 1)
      - "Tenderfoot," 25-39. February 1935 (Box 1)
      - "Bonanza," 100-127. April 1935 (Box 1)
      - "Muleshoes for Luck," 34-49. June 1935 (Box 1)
      - "Phantom Gunman," 99-120. August 1935 (Box 1)
      - "Squawman's Daughter," 105-123. October 1935 (Box 1)
      - "Rough Canyon Red," 31-39. December 1935 (Box 1)
      - "The Sheepherder," 86-116. February 1936 (Box 2)
      - "Gringo Gold," 18-51. April 1936 (Box 2)
      - "The Kid Collects," xiii/8: 3-27. June 1936 (Box 2)
      - "Last of the Wild Bunch," 106-118. August 1936 (Box 2)
      - "Hell on the Prod," 88-121. September 1936 (Box 2)
      - "The Devil's Deputy," 82-115. October 1936 (Box 2)
      - "Gun Gambler," 76-114. November 1936 (Box 2)
      - "Lead Re-Union," 104-115. December 1936 (Box 2)
      - "Son of the Owl Hoot," 65-80. January 1937 (Box 2)
      - "Red Rock Rannihan," 78-112. February 1937 (Box 2)
      - "Winner Take All," 53-63. April 1937 (Box 2)
      - "Renegade Rancho," 78-120. June 1937 (Box 2)
      - "The Owlhoot Route," 102-121. August 1937 (Box 2)
      - "Powdersmoke Pardners," 68-98. October 1937 (Box 2)
      - "Powder Born," 50-65. December 1937 (Box 2)
      - "Cut Loose the colts," xiv/9: 91-117. February 1938 (Box 2)
      - "The Gun Boss of Lost Ranchero," 38-68. April 1938 (Box 2)
      - "Powder to Burn," 90-121. June 1938 (Box 2)
      - "The Devil's Trigger Pard," 92-123. August 1938 (Box 2)
      - "The War-Bonnet Mavericks," 90-124. October 1938 (Box 2)
      - "Blood on the Border Moon," 98-126. April 1939 (Box 2)
      - "Brand of the Killer," 94-128. July 1939 (Box 2)
      - "Heritage of the Owlhoot Trail," xv/6: 3-63. October 1939 (Box 2)
      - "Sagebrush and Six-Guns," 31-72. December 1939 (Box 2)
      - "Senor Scarface," 98-127. April 1940 (Box 2)
      - "Boss of the Border Clan," 109-128. June 1940 (Box 2)
      - "Satan Empties a Saddle," 46-60. August 1940 (Box 2)
      - "Riders of the Whistling Wind," 94-126. October 1940 (Box 2)
      - "Fate Fans a .45," 108-128. December 1940 (Box 2)
      - "Canyon of the Damned," 3-31. February 1941 (Box 2)
      - "Colt Angel of Rancho Diablo," 107-128. April 1941 (Box 2)
      - "Sudden Guns," 94-128. June 1941 (Box 2)
      - "Pilgrim of the Rio," 86-126. August 1941 (Box 2)
      - "Two-Bits a Badge Man," 110-128. October 1941 (Box 2)
      - "Gringo Guns," 86-128. December 1941 (Box 2)
      - "Guns of the Dawn Rider," xvi/8: 3-73. February 1942 (Box 2)
      - "The Death Brand-Gringo," 92-121. April 1942 (Box 2)
      - "The Buckaroo from Brimstone," 75-86. August 1942 (Box 2)
      - "Cross-Breeds Gamble," 68-79. December 1942 (Box 2)
      - "Coward's Draw," 39. Summer 1943 (Box 2)
      - "Raiders of Longhorn Empire," 52-65. February 1943 (Box 2)
      - "Six-Gun Ghost From Robbers' Roost," 72-88. April 1943 (Box 2)
    - Adventure
      - "The Grub Line," 150-176. 1924 (Box 2)
      - "Worked Brands," 59-72. July 1924 (Box 2)
      - "Deuce High," 136-145. March 1925 (Box 2)
      - "Paid Off," lii/iv: 3-44. July 10,1925 (Box 2)
      - "The Fallacy of 'Faro'," 170-187. December 23,1926 (Box 2)
      - "El Caballero," 2-47. June 1,1928 (Box 2)
      - "A Notched Gun," 20-25. 1928 (Box 2)
      - "Empty Shells, 122-132. 1928 (Box 2)
      - "Center-Fire Pride," 30-42. September 11,1929 (Box 2)
      - "The Orneriest Three," 27-38. 1929 (Box 2)
      - "Iron Sombrero," 28-39. 1930 (Box 2)
      - "The Mister," 62-72. December 1,1932 (Box 2)
      - "Sorry Sam, Cowhand," 40-49. January 1,1933 (Box 2)
      - "The Squarehead," 103-113. September 1,1934 (Box 2)
      - "Cotton Top," 78-89. December 1938 (Box 2)
      - "Town Tamer," 36-73. June 1939 (Box 2)
      - "Dally Man," 60-73. 1941 (Box 2)
      - "Round-Up and Sun Prarie," 10-40. April 1942 (Box 2)
    - Ace-High Western Magazine
      - "Dead Man's Line-Camp," 54-69. August 1936 (Box 3)
      - "Cotton Top Crowds His Luck," 52-72. October 1936 (Box 3)
      - "The Horseman from Hades," 54-74. November 1936 (Box 3)
      - "The Owlhoot Sky Pilot," 50-67. December 1936 (Box 3)
      - "The Owlhoot Sky Pilot, Part II," 78-97. January 1937 (Box 3)
      - "The Owlhoot Sky Pilot, Part III," 76-94. February 1937 (Box 3)
      - "The Owlhoot Sky Pilot, Part IV," 76-92. March 1937 (Box 3)
      - "The Owlhoot Sky Pilot, Part V," 78-98. April 1937 (Box 3)
      - "The Owlhoot Sky Pilot, Part VI," 82-100. May 1937 (Box 3)
      - "Valley of Missing Men," 8-11. July 1937 (Box 3)
      - "Gun Guard for a Ghost Town," 62-80. August 1937 (Box 3)
      - "Ghost Boss of the Mutiny Trail Crew," 38-56. October 1937 (Box 3)
      - "Gun Hire for Hunted Men," 10-36. December 1937 (Box 3)
      - "Prairie Fire Boss," 8-28. January 1949 (Box 3)
    - All Western Magazine
      - "Feud Valley, Part I," 6-28. November 1933 (Box 3)
      - "Feud Valley, Part I," 7/20: 97-114. December 1933 (Box 3)
      - "Feud Valley, Part I," 7/21:93-109. January 1934: (Box 3)
      - "The Rawhide Kid," 9/27: 26-33. July 1936 (Box 3)
      - "The Rough String," 6-23. April 1936 (Box 3)
      - "Whoop and Holler," 17/49: 8-55. May 1936 (Box 3)
    - Air Stories
      - "Broken Wings," 1-42. No Date (Box 3)
    - Argosy
      - "Sons of Gun Fighters," 4-105. October 14, 1933 (Box 3)
      - "Fenced Off," 247/3: 30-62. June 2, 1934 (Box 3)
      - "Brothers of the Gun, part I," 302/1: 6-23. September 1940 (Box 3)
      - "Black Fire, Part I," 302/6: 6-22. October 19, 1940 (Box 3)
      - "Black Fire, Conclusion," 303/1: 94-98. October 26, 1940 (Box 3)
      - "The Whisper Trail, part I," 6-24. February 10, 1940 (Box 3)
      - "The Whisper Trail, Conclusion," 297/1: 108-127. February 17, 1940 (Box 3)
      - "Watered Guns, part I," 299/2: 22-44. May 18,1940 (Box 3)
      - "Watered Guns, conclusion," 299/3: 95-110. May 25, 1940 (Box 3)
      - "Wet Beef from Mexico, part I," 306/6: 6-15. April 5, 1941 (Box 3)
      - "Night Ride," 308/5: 6-21. June 21, 1941 (Box 3)
      - "Town Marshall," 310/1: 6-65. August 16, 1941 (Box 3)
      - "Town Marshall, conclusion," 310/2: 56-65. August 23, 1941 (Box 3)
    - Avon Western Reader
      - "Emptied Guns," 41-71. 1947 (Box 3)
    - Badman Annual
      - "No Re-Ride," 11-12. 1971 (Box 4)
      - "Dual Hanging in Arizona," 40-43. 1971 (Box 4)
    - Big-Book Western
      - "The Z Lightening Strikes," 8-38. April 1946 (Box 4)
      - "When Hell Hit Horsethief Crossing," 10-26. August 1946 (Box 4)
      - "The Wolf-Cub Fights Alone," 10-32. September 1946 (Box 4)
      - "That Bloody Brimstone Border," 10-23. November 1946 (Box 4)
      - "The Devil's Pitchfork," 10-33. December 1946 (Box 4)
      - "The Ghost of One-Eye Bogard," 8-27. March 1947 (Box 4)
      - "Little Doc's .30-30 Quarantine," 6-24. July 1947 (Box 4)
      - "Cowmen Take Plenty Killing," 6-30. December 1947 (Box 4)
      - "Load Your guns for the Border Devil," 6-28. July 1948 (Box 4)
      - "When the Gun-Wolves Howl," 6-23. September 1948 (Box 4)
      - "Gun-Wolf in Sheeper's Duds," 10-28. October 1948 (Box 4)
      - "Son of a He-Wolf," 8-26. November 1948 (Box 4)
      - "Play the Gunsmoke Joker," 14-35. December 1948 (Box 4)
      - "Head North, Killer!," 8-27. January 1949 (Box 4)
      - "Gun-Brothers on the Rio," 10-27. March 1949 (Box 4)
    - Black Aces
      - "Lobo," 1/2: 27-39. February 1932 (Box 4)
    - Blazing Guns Western Story Magazine
      - "Hell with a Running Iron," no.1: 1-45. October 1954 (Box 4)
    - Detective Story Magazine
      - "Man-Afraid-of-His-Horses," LXII/1: 108-114. November 10. 1923 (Box 4)
    - Dime Western
      - "Tundro's Darkness," 36-47. December 1932 (Box 5)
      - "Boot Hill Epitaph," 37-49. January 1933 (Box 5)
      - "The Passing of Poker Joe," 8-24. February 1933 (Box 5)
      - "Son of a Gunman," 43-53. March 1933 (Box 5)
      - "Bullet Tally," 47-57. April 1933 (Box 5)
      - "Outlaws Three," 41-51. May 1933 (Box 5)
      - "Owlhooter," 38-48. June 1933 (Box 5)
      - "Guns Below the Border," 50-70. October 1933 (Box 5)
      - "Brothers of Battle," 29-42. November 1933 (Box 5)
      - "Brand of the Badlands," 10-36. December 1933 (Box 5)
      - "Outlawed!," 8-33. January 1934 (Box 5)
      - "Hoot-Owl Pool," 12-41. February 1934 (Box 5)
      - "The Hell-Creek Maverick," 12-41. March 1934 (Box 5)
      - "Cowman's Law," 12-31. April 1934 (Box 5)
      - "Outlawed Orphan," 10-38. May 1934 (Box 5)
      - "Maverick Men," 12-41. June 1934 (Box 5)
      - "The Death of Maverick," 12-38. July 1934 (Box 5)
      - "Men of the Dark Trails," 12-41. August 1934 (Box 5)
      - "Rimrock Renegades," 12-42. September 1934 (Box 5)
      - "Death Rides Herd," 52-67. September 15, 1934 (Box 5)
      - "Black Outlaw," 54-68. October 1, 1934 (Box 5)
      - "Brand Blotters' Blood Tally," 10-39. November 1, 1934 (Box 5)
      - "Three Outlaws Meet," 52-67. November 15, 1934 (Box 5)
      - "Rio Renegade," 10-42. December 15, 1934 (Box 5)
      - "Creed of the Lawless," 10-39. January 1, 1935 (Box 5)
      - "The Concho Kid Pays Off," 54-69. January 15, 1935 (Box 5)
      - "Satan's Saddle Mate," 10-43. February 15, 1935 (Box 5)
      - "Ghost Guns of Black Coulee," 8-37. March 1, 1935 (Box 5)
      - "Dead Man's Drift Fence," 54-73. March 15, 1935 (Box 5)
      - "The Rolling-R Rides to Glory," 44-61. April 1, 1935 (Box 5)
      - "Badlands Orphan," 8-39. April 15, 1935 (Box 5)
      - "Six Gringos Ride to Hell," 6-38. May 1, 1935 (Box 5)
      - "Branded Men," 52-68. May 15, 1935 (Box 5)
      - "Fate for a Lawman," 46-63. June 1, 1935 (Box 5)
      - "Feud Guns of Brady's Basin," 6-37. June 15, 1935 (Box 5)
      - "The Partner of Buckshot Blue," 6-34. July 1, 1935 (Box 5)
      - "Wanted Man's Gamble," 40-55. July 15, 1935 (Box 5)
      - "Badlands Lawman!," 6-35. August 1, 1935 (Box 5)
      - "Son of the Owlhoot," 6-35. August 15, 1935 (Box 5)
      - "Tom Ball - Gun-Doctor," 10-42. October 1, 1935 (Box 5)
      - "Gunsmoke Born," 10-40. October 15, 1935 (Box 5)
      - "Wild Buck Lawman," 12-39. November 1, 1935 (Box 5)
      - "Gun Ghosts of Skull Creek," 12-43. December 1, 1935 (Box 5)
      - "Vigilante Vengeance," 54-73. February 1936 (Box 5)
      - "Wild Men in Buckskin," 10-38. March 1936 (Box 5)
      - "Missouri River Renegade," 10-39. April 1936 (Box 5)
      - "Six-gun Quarantine," 8-39. May 1936 (Box 5)
      - "The Dead-Game Tinhorn," 8-34. June 1936 (Box 5)
      - "The Badlands Vigilante," 8-38. July 1936 (Box 5)
      - "The Button Rides to War," 8-35. August 1936 (Box 5)
      - "Trail Herd to Perdition," 8-41. September 1936 (Box 5)
      - "The Wagon Train Feud," 10-40. October 1936 (Box 5)
      - "A new Marshal for Pinto," 10-40. November 1936 (Box 5)
      - "Gun-Cub of the Black Wolf," 8-37. January 1937 (Box 5)
      - "Strawboss for the Damned," 10-41. March 1937 (Box 5)
      - "A Renegade Rules the S-C Ranch," 10-40. April 1937 (Box 5)
      - "Death Rides with the Black Fergusons," 10-40. May 1937 (Box 5)
      - "The Gringo Who Wouldn't Die," 10-42. June 1937 (Box 5)
      - "Last Stand of the Gila Pool Cowmen," 8-38. July 1937 (Box 5)
      - "A Gun Ghost Runs to Rimrock," 8-38. August 1937 (Box 5)
      - "Lone Wolf of the Feud Pack," 10-39. September 1937 (Box 5)
      - "The Raw, Red Trail to Dodge!," 10-42. October 1937 (Box 5)
      - "Trail Herd's Gunsmoke Market," 10-40. November 1937 (Box 5)
      - "Sun Prairie's Revival," 10-40. December 1937 (Box 5)
      - "Guns Break Trail for a Texan's Herd," 8-42. January 1938 (Box 5)
      - "Death Waits West of Dodge," 8-36. February 1938 (Box 5)
      - "Rawhide, Gunsmoke and Texas Cattle!," 10-41. March 1938 (Box 5)
      - "Stepson of the Wild Bunch," 8-40. April 1938 (Box 5)
      - "His Partner, The Gun-Chost," 8-36. May 1938 (Box 5)
      - "The Badlands Send a Fighting Man," 8-45. June 1938 (Box 5)
      - "Signed on to Die!," 6-38. July 1938 (Box 5)
      - "Fear God and Shoot Straight," 46-64. August 1938 (Box 5)
      - "Owlhoot Makes a Cowman," 8-41. September 1938 (Box 5)
      - "Doc Masters' Last Gun Deal," 8-42. October 1938 (Box 5)
      - "The Gunsmoke Cub Finds a Brand," 9-32. November 1938 (Box 5)
      - "Recruit of the Hang-Noose Syndicate," 11-34. December 1938 (Box 5)
      - "The Trail Drive God Forgot," 8-40. January 1939 (Box 5)
      - "Braking of the Horse Thief Pool," 9-36. February 1939 (Box 5)
      - "Gun Call for the Wind-River Riders," 13-44. March 1939 (Box 5)
      - "The Square Dealer Last Chance," 11-44. April 1939 (Box 5)
      - "Gunsmoke Bonus for Stolen Beef," 9-44. May 1939 (Box 5)
      - "Button Brewster Rides to War," 9-40. June 1939 (Box 5)
      - "Lone Pike's Last Gunsmoke Sermon," 7-36. July 1939 (Box 5)
      - "Marked with Satan's Road Brand," 7-36. August 1939 (Box 5)
      - "The Summer of Black Snow," 48-67. September 1939 (Box 5)
      - "Free bullets for the Quick-Grave Legion," 6-45. October 1939 (Box 5)
      - "Gun-Guide for Satan's Border-Jumpers," 8-39. November 1939 (Box 5)
      - "Gray Wool Brings Gunsmoke!," 8-38. December 1939 (Box 5)
      - "War-Smoke Guides the Westward Mails," 4-41. January 1940 (Box 6)
      - "New Graves at Hide-Out Ranch," 44-58. February 1940 (Box 6)
      - "Gunsmoke Key for the Padlocked Deadline," 6-40. March 1940 (Box 6)
      - "Too 'Soft' for the Owlhoot," 36-50. April 1940 (Box 6)
      - "Gun-Partners of Overland Mail," 6-39. May 1940 (Box 6)
      - "Smoke McGonigal's Last Gun-Chore," 46-64. June 1940 (Box 6)
      - "Gun-Call for Buckskin Warriors," 6-38. July 1940 (Box 6)
      - "Murder Boss of Wagon Wheel Ranch," 38-55. August 1940 (Box 6)
      - "A Greenhorn Rides the Death-Watch," 6-65. September 1940 (Box 6)
      - "The Fighting Flaggs Ride at Midnight," 8-35. November 1940 (Box 6)
      - "The Bear Paw Man-Breaker," 42-55. October 1940 (Box 6)
      - "The Mad Gunman ofWolf Tooth Point," 46-68. December 1940 (Box 6)
      - "Mutiny at Longrider Camp," 8-36. January 1941 (Box 6)
      - "Greenhorns Can Be Tough," 44-60. February 1941 (Box 6)
      - "The Double Circle Invasion," 8-36. March 1941 (Box 6)
      - "Courage of the Barnaby Clan," 8-37. May 1941 (Box 6)
      - "Blood Ransoms the Snake Track Ranch," 10-38. June 1941 (Box 6)
      - "A New Sheriff for Sagebrush Flat," 46-62. August 1941 (Box 6)
      - "The Pinto Basin Renegades," 10-35. September 1941 (Box 6)
      - "Those Feudin' Garveys!," 44-64. October 1941 (Box 6)
      - "Way for a Ranger," 11-31. November 1941 (Box 6)
      - "There's Hell in the Badlands," 11-36. December 1941 (Box 6)
      - "Manhunt!," 58-72. January 1942 (Box 6)
      - "That Bloody Sangria Trial!," 10-38. February 1942 (Box 6)
      - "Gun-Riot at Dry Gulch," 11-29. March 1942 (Box 6)
      - "Saga of the Outlaw Kid," 10-41. April 1942 (Box 6)
      - "Wet Cattle-Hot Guns!," 58-74. May 1942 (Box 6)
      - "Last Call for Diamond-A Fighting Men," 10-36. June 1942 (Box 6)
      - "Draw Your Pay in Hell!," 52-68. July 1942 (Box 6)
      - "Dower Rights to Gunsmoke Ranch," 10-38. September 1942 (Box 6)
      - "The Affairs at Horse Thief Crossing," 48-62. October 1942 (Box 6)
      - "Dry Lightening," 12-38. November 1942 (Box 6)
      - "New Hands for Shanghai Kelly!," 46-61. December 1942 (Box 6)
      - "Christmas at Mormon Basin," 11-34. January 1943 (Box 6)
      - "Hell Starts at Pulpito," 48-66. February 1943 (Box 6)
      - "Hell Rides the Grizzly Gulch Stage," 10-35. March 1943 (Box 6)
      - "Killer Without a Name," 9-32. April 1943 (Box 6)
      - "The Boothill Joker," 54-70. May 1943 (Box 6)
      - "Though Hand!," 8-32. June 1943 (Box 6)
      - "Boss of Outlaw Crossing," 58-76. July 1943 (Box 6)
      - "Back Trail to Gun-Trouble," 8-34. September 1943 (Box 6)
      - "Gun-Squatter' Rights," 10-36. October 1943 (Box 6)
      - "Hot Lead for the Humpback Syndicate," 8-30. November 1943 (Box 6)
      - "Tough Hands Wanted!," 36-52. December 1943 (Box 6)
      - "Five Keys to Hell's Home Ranch," 8-32. January 1944 (Box 6)
      - "The War-Smokes Tell of Blood!," 8-27. March 1944 (Box 6)
      - "Rimrock's Gunsmoke Ressurection," 8-22. April 1944 (Box 6)
      - "Last of the Range-War Outcasts," 30-41. May 1944 (Box 6)
      - "Teh Devil of Paradise Valley," 8-26. June 1944 (Box 6)
      - "Those Badlands Feud-Busters!," 8-19. July 1944 (Box 6)
      - "The Anvil's Fourth Killer," 8-27. August 1944 (Box 6)
      - "Boot-Tough, Snake-Mean!," 10-20. September 1944 (Box 6)
      - "Gun-Wages for Wild Bill Williams," 10-25. October 1944 (Box 6)
      - "They Knew no Law!," 10-23. December 1944 (Box 6)
      - "Remember Toscosa!," 10-25. January 1945 (Box 6)
      - "Born to Gunsmoke!," 8-25. February 1945 (Box 6)
      - "Bushwhack War for Sale!," 10-25. March 1945 (Box 6)